<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<entry>

    <item>
        <id>1</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title>
        <desc>Kavingar with Brother A.L. Srinivasan- Film producer and Film Chamber President five terms.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>2</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title>
        <desc>Kavingar’s 50th Birthday celebrations in Madurai. It was organised by Mr.Nedumaran, standing next to him.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>3</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>M.G.R and Kavingar were great friends and also on certain political grounds, they differed. But the sincerity to each other was well known. All the songs of M.G.R were hits.</desc>
        <image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>4</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>M.R.Radha- a good friend as well as well wisher of Kavingar. He acted in Kavingars’ ‘Kavalai Illatha Manithan’ film.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>5</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Kavingar had many functions and meetings.</desc><image>R.drawable.k5</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>6</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title>
        <desc>KANNADHASAN MANIMANDABAM- Karaikudi has Kavingar’s photos, and library and also hosts meetings on Kavingar.</desc><image>R.drawable.k6</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>7</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title>
        <desc>Mrs. Parvathi Kannadhasan- She was the back bone of Kavingar. Took care of the house and was a fantastic culinary expert.</desc>
        <image>R.drawable.k7</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>8</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title>
        <desc>Rare photo:Sitting From Left: Kavingar’s sister’s daughter Manimegalai, Ponnammal Kannadhasan,Center Kavingar’s Sister Kannamai Aachi, Vallikannu, And Parvathi Kannadhasan. STANDING: Kavingar’s Sister Sornam, Muthu her husband, Somasundaram Chettiar husband of Kannammai Aachi, Karaikudi Assistant Anjezhuthu</desc>
        <image>R.drawable.k8</image>
    </item>



    <item>
        <id>9</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Moods of Kavingar are well known.</desc><image>R.drawable.k9</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>10</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>He loves to pose for camera. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>11</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Nowadays all these photographs convey a meaning.  </desc><image>R.drawable.k11</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>12</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>That is the way he thinks. Look at the eyes. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>13</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>His favourite leader Kamarajar</desc><image>R.drawable.k13</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>14</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>This Poet used to write, when he has the option. But always it was dictated. He had the speed in both. His  favorite chair is in the Kannadhasan Pathippagam.</desc><image>R.drawable.k14</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>15</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>At the wedding of his daughter, with the then Hon. C.M. Kalaingar Karunanithi and Minister Mr.Sadhik Batcha.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>16</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Kavingar was a foodie. He loved to eat. Variety but in small quantity. A dinner in Malaysia.</desc><image>R.drawable.k16</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>17</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>The one real HERO Kavingar admired and the one and only KAVINGAR , M.G.R. admired. Kavingar wrote story, screen play ,dialogue and some songs for seven films  of M.G.R.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>18</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Making the poet as POETLAUREATE .  The Honourable C.M. M.G.R. announces the proposal of his Government to nominater Kavingar as ARASAVAIK KAVINGAR. At the wedding reception of his son Gandhi Kannadhasan</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>19</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>The one and only actor, Kavinagr introduced in films. Manorama Aachi-  Balachander, The Great had said all his introduced heroes and heroines are good but cannot match the one Kannadhasan introduced.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>20</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>With the Russian Poet, when Kavingar was the President of Indo- Soviet Cultural Society.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>21</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Catch them young ! Director Sridher, Sivaji, Chandrababu, M.S.V and Kavingar. Films that ran for 100 days in ten theaters only celebrated the function.</desc><image>R.drawable.k21</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>22</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>This App is a gift to you. Where can you see such young  Sivaji, Kannadhasan. M.S.Viswanathan and Ramamoorthy. At the film PASAMALAR 25th week celebrations. The picture ran in 67 theaters in All over Tamil Nadu.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>23</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Friends and Foes – They were so close that became their bond that was not seen by all. They fought and yet they were good friends.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>24</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>The C.M and the King of Poets.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>25</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Kannadhasan’s contribution to the growth of DMK is well known among the elderly. But this generation to know, this picture will help.Kannadhasna with MGR, Kalaingar, Anbil Dharmalingam and Mathiyalagan.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>26</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Only Kannadhasan must write my films songs, Sivaji used to say. Can you feel the closeness they have?</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>27</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>The swearing in ceremony of Kavingar as ARASAVAIK KAVINAGR in Rajaji Hall. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>28</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>The songs of Kannahdasan. A visual treat to see the composing of songs. He will deliver the lyrics as soon as the tune is given. With Music Director K.V.Mahadevan, Director G.R.Nathan and dialogue Writer  Valampuri Somanathan.</desc><image>R.drawable.k28</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>29</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>With the Russian Poets.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>30</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>With the Central Minister of Information  and Broadcasting Mr.Ragunath Reddy. Kannahdhasan was the bridge between the Governements.  Many Ministers were his friends and he spent for them. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>31</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Lyrics to tune OR Tune the lyrics. It was easy for both Kavingar and Mellisai Mannar M.S.V.Can you see the height difference
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>32</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>1976, the 50th Birthday Celebrations of Kavinagr in Madurai. Mr.Nedumaran of Congress made a great function. And you can see the Vallal Chinnappa Devar and Music Directors Shankar Ganesh.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>33</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Gandhi Kannadhasan wedding reception. The CM attends.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>34</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>At the function of Attaukkara Alamelu. CM. R.M.Veerappan and Chinnappa Devar and Kannadhasan in consultation.  That is how MGR ties [tightens]  his Veshti. </desc><image>R.drawable.k35</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>35</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>They both came out of DMK due the power struggle and back biting. Both were not after anything but Annadorai. These two were more popular and next to Anna. Read it all in Kavingar’s book VANAVASAM.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>36</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Kavingar created many directors. Among them, Madurai Thirumaran is one.Mrs. Paravthi Kannadhasan’s sister’s daughter was married to Thirumaran. And the wedding and the reception at Woodlands Hotel was conducted by Kavinagr. You can see Gandhi Kannadhasan at the rights side corner and in the middle is Annadorai Kannadhasan, in suite.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>37</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Do you know that Kannadhasan conducted and took the Thaali and gave it to Sivaji to tie on Kamala Amma ,in the wedding? An  honour that was bestowed by the Family of Sivaji on the Poet for the gift of his poesy. Here with MGR and Kalaingar at the Wedding.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>38</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>KARUPPUPANAM- a film none of the heroes wanted to act. A s it dealt with the Black Money laundering. So, Kavingar acted as the hero cum good villain. A Robin Hood style story. See the film in TV- shown regularly- you can see how majestic he walks and sweet he delivers his dialogues.</desc><image>R.drawable.k38</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>39</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>More than his Gods, Kavinagr loved his Mother and Father. This photo adorns, even now, in his bed room. Kavinagr will wake up looking at this picture and will not see any one till then. His Mother VISALKAKSHI and Father SATHAPPAN
        </desc><image>R.drawable.k39</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>40</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Photo apps ,with comments compiled and presented  by Gandhi Kannadhasan, son of the Poet.</desc>
        <image>R.drawable.k40</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>41</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Do you remember ‘ULLATHIL NALLA ULLAM’ song? That was sung by this singer Sirgazhli Govindarajan.  Honored by Raj Sir Muthiah Chettiyar.
        </desc><image>R.drawable.k41</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>42</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Thanks! Kannadhasan used to call MGR as SAAMI. A passionate calling and MGR love it.</desc>
        <image>R.drawable.k42</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>43</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>A profile of Kavingar. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>44</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Daily Thanthi , a daily started by Adhithanar was Kavingar’s favourite news paper.Mr. Sivanthi Aadhithan succeeded and he was a close friend of Kannadhasan. This kind of unusual request Kaviingar will do for friends only. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>45</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>At Sivanthi Aadhithan’s office with Editor and  good friend Mr.Shanmuganathan.  He still remains the best friend of the Family of Kavingar.</desc><image>R.drawable.k45</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>46</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>A great picture. Kamalahasan celebrated his 100th film. And wanted to thank all who were with him.The shield says ‘NANDRI’. CM M.G.R and Kavingar presided over the function.</desc>
        <image>R.drawable.k46</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>47</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Vijaya Fims and Studios  owner Mr.Nagi Reddi , a Telugu man, was a great admirer of Kannadhasan. His Sivaj starrer was Vasantha maligai. And MGR starrer was Enga Veettu Pillai.</desc><image>R.drawable.k47</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>48</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>No film Lyricist then and now had that much friends in Politics. Kannadhasan was a King among poets even with the political circles.  The respect came as no surprise as Kannadhasan’s pen was mightier than sward.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>49</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Kavingar’s  favorite film team. Director Sridhar  with MSV in Sumaithangi film composing at Chtralaya’s  office.Co- producer Kovai Chezhiyan is also seen.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>50</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Sampath and Kannadhasan. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>51</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Repeat</desc><image>R.drawable.k51</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>52</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>The fight against Chinese aggressors. Kavingar was the given to lead a team of artists and musicians to the border to entertain our Jawans. They all went to Thanlaivar Kamaraj’s house. </desc>
        <image>R.drawable.k52</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>53</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>“SERAMAN KAADHALI” - got him the SAHITYA ACADEMY AWARD. Interestingly this historical novel was written by Kavingar at the initiation of Kanchi MAHA PERIYAVA. His blessings was always with Kavingar.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>54</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Can you see the look in his eyes? His concentration is great when he answer you.  </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>55</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Supre Star Rajini. The film Aarilirunthu Aarubathu Varaai 100 days function.You can never see a photo of Super Star touching the feet of the other. He always loved the Tamil and lyrics of Kavingar and admired him. A great picture to speak in the future also.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>56</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Kavingar poses without any inhibition. Always casual. </desc><image>R.drawable.k57</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>56</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>L.R.Eswari Singing in a Temple. She is known for her Amman songs.Kavingar presides over.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>58</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>REPEAT</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>59</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>REPEAT</desc><image>R.drawable.k56</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>60</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>CHO- acted in Kavingar produced movies. He was a great friend. He interviews Kavingar for Kumudham. This interview is in the book KANNADHASAN PETTIGAL.
    </desc><image>R.drawable.k60</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>61</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>VANAVASAM - popular edition was brought out by Kavingar himself. This edition was released by Thalaivar Kamaraj. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>62</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Kavingar’s first wedding. Mrs. Ponnammal Kannadhasan. Traditional attire. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>63</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>The Maharaja ! With his wives Parvathi and Ponnammal. They all lived as ‘One Happy Family’.With all the children in the same house.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>64</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>The friend. Sivanthi Aadhithyan of Dinathanthi. Receives Kavingar when Kavingar went to their office.
    </desc><image>R.drawable.k64</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>65</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Pulavar Naga.Shanmugam was  his friend.</desc><image>R.drawable.k65</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>66</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>REPEAT</desc><image>R.drawable.k66</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>67</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>REPEAT</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>68</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>With his ever loving Thambi. Mellisai Mannar M.S.V. A rare color still taken for the BOMMAI = TAmil cinema magazine.
    </desc><image>R.drawable.k68</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>69</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Honoring Viswanathan - Ramamoorthy. Must be PASAMALAR film. AS all of them are young.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>70</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>When Kavingar went to Russia. He wrote poems on the Russians. With the dance group, that performed for the ISCUS delegation.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>71</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Friendship was always love and fight. These two greats remained that way.</desc><image>R.drawable.k71</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>72</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>The family that live together love each other. This photo in the 1960’s show how Kavingar lived with all his children and two wives in one house at Kannadhasan Salai.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>73</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>God has descended to see the composing of Kavingar. That is what other language Lyricists say about Kavingar. This is one such moment.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>74</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Russian Poet and Kavingar.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>75</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>With Fr.George and Fr.Stanislas in Trichy. Kavingar wrote YESU KAAVIYAM in two weeks and the effort and support of these two Reverends is commendable.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>76</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>REPEAT</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>77</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>REPEAT</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>78</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>REPEAT</desc><image>R.drawable.k78</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>79</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>‘Ulaga Nayagan’ Kamal Hassan wanted to thank the film industry for the 100 films he completed. The then CM and The Poet Laureate of his Government. In a serious discussion on the stage. The memento on the table speak ample about Kamal Sir.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>80</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Mount Road GPO. Kavingar leads the protest against State Government. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>81</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>WRONG STILL</desc><image>R.drawable.k81</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>82</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>WRONG STILL</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>83</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Kavingar’s  hand writing. For a film company he had written this. After 1960. Kavingar dictated lyrics to his first assistant Panchu Arunachalam. And that went till last. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>84</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>With the CM Mr.Bakthavatchalam and the former CM Thalaivar Kamaraj. Kavingar  demand the most respect in the political circles.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>85</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>With his grandson Kartheck Kannadhasan. Gandhi Kannadhasan’s son. Whenever Kavingar had time, he would play with his grandson. Age was no bar to the Poet</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>86</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>The then Governor Mr.Prabudas Patwari. And with ‘Vanathi’ Thirunavukkarasu.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>87</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>More of Kavingar with the Thalaivar</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>88</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Thalaivar Kamaraj,  Central Minister VK Krishna Menon, Raja Sir Muthiah Chettiar. E.V.K. Sampath, Minister Poovaragavan. Occasion and location not available.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>89</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>With Thalaivar and Nadigar Thilagam  on stage. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>90</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>With his favourite leader.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>91</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>During the regime of MGR as CM, he made Kavingar as the Poet Laureate of the Tamil Nadu Government. This post was vacant for more than three decades after Sri.Namakkal Ramalinagam Pillai.  This car was given by the Government for Kavingar TMY 5050.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>92</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>A colored portrait.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>93</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>PASAMALAR celebrated  25 weeks. The fans celebrated it all over Tamil Nadu. The actors and the Technicians and Kavingar were always part of it. They respected their audience that much. With Sivaji and Savirithri.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>94</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Same stage. With Sivaji, Gemini Ganesan, Director Sridhar, Chandra Babu and Savitri.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>95</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Not sure of the occasion.With Kamaraj are KAvingar, A.L.S, Sivaji, Padmini, J.Jayalitha, Rajasulochana, Padmini and P.Suseela
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>96</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>With the Pulavar Tamil Kanal  attending a meeting in a college in Tirunelveli.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>97</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Brothers. Same height, fair and spotlessly dressed, most respected in the Tamil and Indian Film Industry. A gifted birth.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>98</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>With the Russian Poets.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>99</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Kannadasan with His wife Parvathi Kannadhasan. They were the greatest hosts to all their relatives and friends. Amma was the back bone of Kavingar, who took all the loads of the house. So Kavingar was free in his mind and body.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>100</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Kannadasan with His wife Poornimal Kannadhasan. A great human being.At the Kannadasan Salai house, you can see the names of these two wives embedded on the enterance.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>101</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Sometimes he used to proof correct his Tamil literary  magazine KANNADHASAN.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>102</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>The cove of the KANNADHASAN KATHAI- a biography of Kavingar came as a serial in Rani Weekly and later as a book.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>103</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>A real photogenic. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>104</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>At the Cresent Park road house, in T.Nagar. Next to the Kannadhasan Salai property. Kavingar with Gandhi and Parvathi with Kamal.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>105</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Rarely you see him with the colored shirt.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>106</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Colored picture</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>107</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Kannadasan, M.G.R at his Son Gandhi Kannadasan’s wedding reception.  </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>108</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Posing for still came naturally.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>109</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Great photo. Kavingar smile is different from others. Slight tilt of the lips to the left can be seen.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>110</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>His favourite pastime reading . He used to in his room. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>111</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>In his room in Kannadhasan salai house.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>112</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>With ‘Paavendar’ BHARATHIDASAN. He and Kavingar were friends as well as foes. Paavendar was against DMK and had difference of opinion. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>113</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>With ‘MozhiGnayiru’  Devaneyapa Paavaanar – Kavingar was given a equal seat in all the Literary Meetings. His elders appreciated the talent in him.</desc><image>R.drawable.k113</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>114</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>With the Actor M.R.Radha- who also acted in Kavingar’s films.  Also political friends.</desc><image>R.drawable.k114</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>115</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>POSES and POSES</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>116</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>CM MGR and Kavingar at the Arasavaik Kavingar installation function.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>117</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Thinker. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>118</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Poses came to him naturally.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>119</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Repeated again. Yes, only to show how much Kavingar was appreciated by the Leaders of yester years. On par with them on stage. A cinema industry man could not achieve this on those days.Kavingar was unique.
        </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>120</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Thanthai  Periyar was the founder of all DMKs. They all came out of his DK party.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>121</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>With EVK Sampath. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>122</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>With the legend JAYAKANTHAN aka JK. These two great writers were very  close friends.JK came to Congress because of Kavingar. </desc><image>R.drawable.k122</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>123</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>A profile.</desc><image>R.drawable.k123</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>124</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>In Rani Chinnammal Road - Film Production Office</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>125</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>In Kavitha Hotel. Where he used to compose many, many songs.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>126</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Kavingar acted in many dramas. All of them Political propaganda and was in favour with the then Congress party. Six dramas were performed by him and he had his own troupe. With Shanmugasundaram in the KONIPPULUGAN GOYABELS. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>127</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Karuppupanam. Film still.</desc><image>R.drawable.k127</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>128</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Kavingar posing for a still.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>129</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>The Guru and the Student.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>130</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>On stage with his last son Venkatachalam. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>131</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Sri Kirupanantha Variar was Kavingar’s spiritual Guru. He had a special place.  He would always attend the  lectures of Variar Swamigal.</desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>


    <item>
        <id>132</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>With CM Kalaingar and ALS. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>133</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>Kamaraj never celebrated his birthdays. But Kavingar would always request him to cut the cake.  Thalaivar would always oblige as he liked Kavingar that much.</desc><image>R.drawable.k133</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>134</id>
        <title>Kannadasan Pathipagam</title><desc>He had his own news papers – THENDRAL  - THENDRAL TIRAI – Alaiosai was his favorite and he wrote for that daily. </desc><image>R.drawable.k134</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>135</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>Kavingar  and his favorite cot. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

    <item>
        <id>136</id>
        <title>Nill</title>
        <desc>A Still to remember……… Kavingar writing on his pad. </desc><image>N/A</image>
    </item>

</entry>